const ExamsData=[
    {   
        title:'Admission Test',
        Author:'Elia_M',
        duration:'25',
        Elia_M:[
            {question:'Which one is a Computer?',
                answer1:'TV',
                answer2:'Mouse',
                answer3:'Keybord',
                correctAnswer:'Tablette'
            },
    
            {question:'The green Apple between the red Apples is Red. Which Apple is Red?',
                answer1:'The two Apples',
                answer2:'The Green Apple',
                answer3:'All of them',
                correctAnswer:'None of the Above'
            },
            
            {question:'The father of Toto has 5 kids; Titi, Tata, Tete, Tuto and ?',
                answer1:'Titi',
                answer2:'Tata',
                answer3:'Tuto',
                correctAnswer:'Toto'
            },
            
            {question:'If 10 Mouses eat one Apple in 10min how many mouses do we need to eat 10 Apples in 100min?',
                answer1:'10',
                answer2:'100',
                answer3:'1000',
                correctAnswer:'None of the Above'
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        title:'Admission Test',
        Author:'Roddrick',
        duration:'25',
        Roddrick:[
            {question:'Which one is a Computer?',
                answer1:'TV',
                answer2:'Mouse',
                answer3:'Keybord',
                correctAnswer:'Tablette'
            },
    
            {question:'The green Apple between the red Apples is Red. Which Apple is Red?',
                answer1:'The two Apples',
                answer2:'The Green Apple',
                answer3:'All of them',
                correctAnswer:'None of the Above'
            },
            
            {question:'The father of Toto has 5 kids; Titi, Tata, Tete, Tuto and ?',
                answer1:'Titi',
                answer2:'Tata',
                answer3:'Tuto',
                correctAnswer:'Toto'
            },
            
            {question:'If 10 Mouses eat one Apple in 10min how many mouses do we need to eat 10 Apples in 100min?',
                answer1:'10',
                answer2:'100',
                answer3:'1000',
                correctAnswer:'None of the Above'
            },
        ]
    },
    {
        title:'Admission Test',
        Author:'Amani',
        duration:'25',
        Amani:[
            {question:'Which one is a Computer?',
                answer1:'TV',
                answer2:'Mouse',
                answer3:'Keybord',
                correctAnswer:'Tablette'
            },
    
            {question:'The green Apple between the red Apples is Red. Which Apple is Red?',
                answer1:'The two Apples',
                answer2:'The Green Apple',
                answer3:'All of them',
                correctAnswer:'None of the Above'
            },
            
            {question:'The father of Toto has 5 kids; Titi, Tata, Tete, Tuto and ?',
                answer1:'Titi',
                answer2:'Tata',
                answer3:'Tuto',
                correctAnswer:'Toto'
            },
            
            {question:'If 10 Mouses eat one Apple in 10min how many mouses do we need to eat 10 Apples in 100min?',
                answer1:'10',
                answer2:'100',
                answer3:'1000',
                correctAnswer:'None of the Above'
            },
        ]
    }
    
    ]
    export default ExamsData